Melich, Tanya M.; Papers apap079
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1944-2017; Undated; 10; 10.4 cubic ft.
  - Abortion, 1972-1999 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Abortion—"That Delicate Balance II: Our Bill of Rights—Life and Choice After Roe v. Wade, 1956/2009 (Video-tape 1)
  - Affirmative Action, 1973-1996; Undated (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Affirmative Action, 1976-1991 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Affirmative Action, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Affirmative Action—92 Forward, 1991-1999; Undated (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 6-7)
  - Affirmative Action—Bakke Case, 1963-1997; Undated (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Africa, 1958-1966; Undated (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - African-Americans—Draft Riots, Interactions With Police, 1966-1968 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - African-Americans—Economic Development, 1969 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - African-American—Extremists, 1960-1967 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - African-Americans—Statistics and Demographic Polls, 1956-2009; Undated (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - African-Americans—Voting, 1959-1972; Undated (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Agriculture in America, 1956-1981 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Business Public Relations, 1981 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Bibliographies, 1975-1976; 1980; Undated (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Breaking the Glass Ceiling, Pat Atkinson-WPOP, 1991 (Cassette 10)
  - Cable—General Information, 1979-1980; Undated (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Campaign Communication in the 1980's, 1982-1983; 1983 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 19-21)
  - Campaign Finance Reform, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 22-24)
  - Children, 1995-1996 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Civil Rights, 1956-1958 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Civil Rights, 1963-1968 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 27-28)
  - Civil Rights, 1963-1973 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Civil Rights, 1985-1990 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Civil Rights, 1987-2000 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Cold War, 1956-1978 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Congress—1960s, 1964-1967 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Congressional District Data Book, 1961 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Conservative Movement, 1974-1977 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Conservative Movement, 1978-1993 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Congressional Record, 1973 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Crime, 1973; Undated (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Direct Election, 1970 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Draft/Conscription, 1966-1973 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Economic Development, 1957-1971 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Economic Development, 1981 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 11-13)
  - Economic Development—Committee for Economic Development, 1962-1965 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Economic Development—Office of Economic Opportunity, 1965 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Emma Awards, 1993 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 16-19)
  - Energy (Materials for NAR)—Newspaper Clippings, 1974-1975 (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 20-21)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1984-1988; Undated (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Equal Rights Amendment—Campaign Kit, 1975; Undated (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Equal Rights Amendment— Cons, 1970-1978; Undated (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Equal Rights Amendment—Election Statistics, 1956-1979; Undated (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Equal Rights Amendment—Extension, 1978; Undated (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 26-27)
  - Equal Rights Amendment—General, 1970-1980; Undated (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Equal Rights Amendment—General and After Failure to Pass, 1971-1999; Undated (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Equal Rights Amendment—Literature, 1973-1978; Undated (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 30-31)
  - Equal Rights Amendment—Organizational Support, 1975-1978; Undated (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Equal Rights Amendment—Post 1975 Defeat, 1975-1979; Undated (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Equal Rights Amendment—Pro, 1974-1984; Undated (Box 2 (10-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Exit Polls, 1996 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Family—State of the Family in America, 1980-1997 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Family Values, 1986-1988 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 3-5)
  - Food Crisis, 1973 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Future—80s, 1975-1981 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 7-8)
  - Future—Issues of the Seventies, 1974-1977; Undated (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Future—Predictions on the World's Future, 1959-1980; Undated (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - GOP Breakthrough in New York City—Press Kit, 1959; 1961; Undated (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Government Research, Bibliography, 1963 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Harvard—Anthony G. Oettinger: Command, Control, Communications and Intelligence (C3I), 1980 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 13-14)
  - Harvard—Computers, 1977-1980; Undated (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 15-16)
  - Harvard—Congress, New Technology Integration into Proceedings, 1980 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Harvard—Dick Newstadt, 1980 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Harvard—Foreign Affairs, 1979-1980 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Harvard—Foreign TV Export, 1980 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Harvard—General Information for Melich Fellowship, 1980 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Harvard—Handouts, 1979-1980 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Harvard—Ideas for Melich Study Group, 1976-1979 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Harvard—Impact of Press on Politics, 1979-1980 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Harvard—Impact of Television on Politics, "Equal Time", 1976-1980; Undated (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 25-26)
  - Harvard—Information Resources Policy Group, 1977-1980 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Harvard—Institute of Politics Leadership Conference, May 8-9, 1987, 1987-1990; Undated (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Harvard—International, 1978-1980; Undated (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Harvard—Iran, 1979-1980 (Box 3 (10-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Harvard—Melich Fellowship, 1979-1980 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 1-2)
  - Harvard—Nieman Fellows, 1979 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Harvard—Notes from Class on Telecommunications, Wyatt, 1979-1980; Undated (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Harvard—People, 1980; Undated (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Harvard—Regulation of New Media, 1979-1980; Undated (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Harvard—Satellites, 1979-1980; Undated (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Harvard—Stu Brotman, Publications and General Information, 1980 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Harvard—Study Group Evaluations (Melich), 1980 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Harvard—Study Group, Guest Lecturer, 1979-1980; Undated (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Harvard—Study Group—Impact of New Broadcasting Technologies on Politics, 1979-1980; Undated (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Harvard—Technology, 1978-1980; Undated (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Health Issues in 2000 Election (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Kennedy Family Tragedies, 1963-1997 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Long Island—Commerce and Industry, 1963 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Melich Resumes, 1983-1996 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - New York City Arts and Culture, 1983-1993; Undated (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - New York City Arts and Culture—Reports to the Mayor, Information from Department of Cultural Affairs, misc., 1983; 1992-1993 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - New York City Budget, 2000 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - New York City Charter Renewal, 1987-1988 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 20-21)
  - New York City—General, 1972-1974; 1985 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - New York City—Handwritten Notes by Melich, Undated (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - New York City Issues, 1973-1974; 1983 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - New York State Government—Privatization Moves, 1993 April (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - New York State Legislature, 1994-1995 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - New York State Legislature—Emphasis on Women's Issues, 1987-1988 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - New York State Legislature, Information on Sex Equity in Education, 1985-1987 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - New York State, Legislature/Legislation, 1990 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - New York state, Legislature/Legislation, 1991 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - New York State, Legislature/Legislation, 1992-1999 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - New York State Legislature/Legislation—Women, 1971-1974 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - New York State Legislature—Women, 1979-1986 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - New York State Legislature/Legislation—Women, 1982-1991 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - New York State Legislature—Various Issues Such as Abortion, Contraception, and Bias-Related Crimes, 1991-1992; Undated (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - New York State Welfare Take-Over (1-4 of 5), 1973 (Box 4 (10-Subject Files), Folder 36-39)
  - New York State Welfare Take-Over (5 of 5), 1973 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - New York Voter Guides, 1989; 1992-1993 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - New York Voter Guides, 1994; 1996-1997 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - New York Voter Guides, 1999; 2001-2002 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - New York Voter Guides, 2001 November 06 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Newspapers About First Space Flight and Moon Landing, 1961; 1969 (Flat-file 1)
  - Newspaper About Moon Landing, 1961; 1969 (Flat-file 2)
  - Obscenity, 1973 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Oswald Ganley Correspondence and Working Paper "United States-Canadian Communications and Information Resources Relationship and its Possible Significance for Worldwide Diplomacy", 1979-1981 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Overpopulation Trends (Newspapers), 1976-1992; Undated (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Panama Canal Opinions on Treaties, 1977; Undated (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Persian Gulf U.S. Involvement, 1987 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Philanthropy—General Information, Emphasis on Women, 1995-2000 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Philanthropy—General Information on Organizations/People, 1986-1999; Undated (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 12-13)
  - Philanthropy—Information on Various Organizations, 1973-1997 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Population—Statistics and Problems, 1959-1998; Undated (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Poverty in America (newspaper), 1977-1992; Undated (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Precinct Education Program—General Information, 1962 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Print and Broadcast Media and the 1st Amendment, 1977-1981; Undated (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Prisons in America, 1974-1976; 1990 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Psychological Behavior (Newspaper), 1976-1991 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Race and Politics in the U.S., 1992-1998; Undated (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Reappointment—Research and General Information on Redistricting in New York, 1990-1992; Undated (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Republican National Committee—News, 1968 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Republican Party—Women, 1976 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Right Wing—California, 1964 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Right Wing—General Information and Views Towards Left, 1963-1970; Undated (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Right Wing—Sixties, 1957-1969; Undated (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 27-28)
  - Right Wing—Sixty-Four Election, 1964; Undated (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Right Wing—Southerners, 1961-1964; Undated (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Sales Tax, 1968 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Scandals, 1989-1997 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - "Science and Government", 1961 (Box 5 (10-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - "Social Policy", 1970-1971 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Soviet Union, 1973 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Tax Cuts—Federal Spending, 1986-1987 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Technologies of the 80s, 1980-1981 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Transborder Data Flows, 1979-1980 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Vietnam, 1973 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - White House, 1974 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Welfare—Proposed Welfare Cuts, News and Opinions, 1979-2002 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 8-9)
  - Women Bios, 1962-2001 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Women—Convention on the Elimination of all Forms of Discrimination Against Women, IWRAW and UN, 1989-1990 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Women and the Economy, 1987-1988 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Women and the Economy, 1988-1994 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Women Executive Appointments, 1983-1993; Undated (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Women—Feminism, 1988-1999 (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Women George Dean—Campaigns to Elect Women to Congress, 1989-2003; Undated (Box 6 (10-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Women Miscellaneous Information, 1980-1985 (Box 7 (10-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Women Miscellaneous Information, 1996 (Box 7 (10-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Women in Politics, 1993-1995; Undated (Box 7 (10-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Women—Polls and Surveys, 1988-1989 (Box 7 (10-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Women's Reproductive Rights, 1991-1995 (Box 7 (10-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Women's Resources, 1985-1998; Undated (Box 7 (10-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Women—Virginia Leadership Conference on the Economy, 1994 January 28-1994 January 30 (Box 7 (10-Subject Files), Folder 7-8)
  - "Women's Voices, A Report", 1992 (Box 7 (10-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - World Population, 1991-1994; Undated (Box 7 (10-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - World's Expo, 1967 (Box 7 (10-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - World War I Poster, Undated (Flat-file 3)
  - Youth and Youth Conferences, 1957-1970 (Box 7 (10-Subject Files), Folder 12)
- Publications, 1967-2007; 11; 3.8 cubic ft.
  This series contains long-term runs of publications collected by Tanya Melich. The two most extensive publications are Hotline Weekly (1994-1997) and The Abortion Report (1992-1997). The Hotline Weekly collected and abbreviated news stories from television, magazine, and newspaper reports relating to politics and government. The Abortion Report was a daily listing of news stories specifically related to abortion, and would be useful for individuals looking to analyze the impact of abortion politics on the nation. The collection of The Abortion Report is not completely inclusive; some dates are missing. This series also contains The Body Politic (1993-1995), Campaign Insider (1997), The Defense Monitor (1984-2002), Ramparts (1967-1970), and The Washington Spectator (1989-2007, with gaps).
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. IV, No. 18, 1992 August (Box 1 (11-Publications), Folder 1)
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. IV, No. 10; Vol. 5, No. 124-130, 1993 December-1994 January (Box 1 (11-Publications), Folder 2)
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. IV, No. 131-159; Vol. IV, No. 82-86, 1994 February-1994 March; 1994 November (Box 1 (11-Publications), Folder 3)
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. VI, No. 105-107, 119-123, 1994 December-1995 January (Box 1 (11-Publications), Folder 4)
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. VI, No. 138-148, 1995 February (Box 1 (11-Publications), Folder 5)
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. VI, No. 152-171, 1995 March (Box 1 (11-Publications), Folder 6)
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. VI, No. 172-183, 1994 April (Box 1 (11-Publications), Folder 7)
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. VI, No. 207, Vol. VI, No. 213-227, 1995 May-1995 June (Box 1 (11-Publications), Folder 8)
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. VI., No. 235, Vol. VII, No.5, 1995 July (Box 1 (11-Publications), Folder 9)
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. VII, No. 12-31, 1995 August (Box 1 (11-Publications), Folder 10-11)
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. VII, No. 32-51, 1995 September (Box 1 (11-Publications), Folder 12-13)
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. VII, No. 52-70, 1995 October (Box 1 (11-Publications), Folder 14-15)
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. VII, No. 73-92, 1995 November (Box 1 (11-Publications), Folder 16)
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. VII, No. 93-106, 1995 December (Box 1 (11-Publications), Folder 17)
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. VII, No. 111-127, 1996 January (Box 1 (11-Publications), Folder 18-19)
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. VII. No. 128-147, 1996 February (Box 1 (11-Publications), Folder 20-21)
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. VII, No. 148-168, 1996 March (Box 1 (11-Publications), Folder 22-23)
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. VII, No. 169-189 (1 of 2), 1996 April (Box 1 (11-Publications), Folder 24)
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. VII, No. 169-189 (2 of 2), 1996 April (Box 2 (11-Publications), Folder 1)
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. VII, No. 190-211, 1996 May (Box 2 (11-Publications), Folder 2-3)
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. VII, No. 212-231, 1996 June (Box 2 (11-Publications), Folder 4-5)
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. VII, No. 233-VIII No. 9, 1996 July (Box 2 (11-Publications), Folder 6-7)
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. VIII, No. 11-31, 1996 August (Box 2 (11-Publications), Folder 8-9)
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. VIII, No. 32-51, 1996 September (Box 2 (11-Publications), Folder 10-11)
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. VIII, No. 52-73, 1996 October (Box 2 (11-Publications), Folder 12-13)
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. VIII, No. 74-92, 1996 November (Box 2 (11-Publications), Folder 14-15)
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. VIII, No. 93-108, 1996 December (Box 2 (11-Publications), Folder 16-17)
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. VIII, No. 109-128, 1997 January (Box 2 (11-Publications), Folder 18-19)
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. VIII, No. 129-147, 1997 February (Box 2 (11-Publications), Folder 20-21)
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. VIII, No. 148-167, 1997 March (Box 2 (11-Publications), Folder 22-23)
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. VIII, No. 168-189, 1997 April (Box 2 (11-Publications), Folder 24-25)
  - The Abortion Report, Vol. VIII, No. 190-197, 1997 May (Box 2 (11-Publications), Folder 26)
  - The Body Politic, Vol. 3, No. 10, Vol. 4, No. 11, Vol 5, No. 1-11, 1993-1995 (Box 3 (11-Publications), Folder 1)
  - The Body Politic, Vol. 6, No. 1-11, 1995 (Box 3 (11-Publications), Folder 2)
  - The Body Politic, Vol. 7, No. 2-11, 1997 (Box 3 (11-Publications), Folder 3)
  - The Body Politic, Vol. 8, No. 1-5, Vol. 9 No. 1-4, 1998-1999 (Box 3 (11-Publications), Folder 4)
  - Campaign Insider, Vol. 1, No. 1-6, 1997 (Box 3 (11-Publications), Folder 5)
  - The Defense Monitor, Vol. XIII, No. 7-8, XIV, No. 10, 1984-1985 (Box 3 (11-Publications), Folder 6)
  - The Defense Monitor, Vol. XV, No. 1-7, Vol. XVI, No. 1-6, 1986-1987 (Box 3 (11-Publications), Folder 7)
  - The Defense Monitor, Vol. XVII, No. 1-5, Vol. XVII, No. 2-8, Vol. XIX, No. 1-9, 1988-1990 (Box 3 (11-Publications), Folder 8)
  - The Defense Monitor, Vol. XX, No. 1-6, Vol. XXI, No. 1-6, Vol. XXII, No. 1-10, 1991-1993 (Box 3 (11-Publications), Folder 9)
  - The Defense Monitor, Vol. XXII, No. 1-9, Vol. XXIV, No. 1-9, 1994-1995 (Box 3 (11-Publications), Folder 10)
  - The Defense Monitor, vol. XXV, No. 1-7, Vol. XXVI, No. 2-6, 1996-1997 (Box 3 (11-Publications), Folder 11)
  - The Defense Monitor, Vol. XXVII, No. 1-2, Vol. XXVIII, No. 2-7, Vol. XXIX, No. 1-10, 1998-2000 (Box 3 (11-Publications), Folder 12)
  - The Defense Monitor, Vol. XXX, No. 2-8, Vol. XXXI, No. 1-4, 2001-2002 (Box 3 (11-Publications), Folder 13)
  - The Hotline Weekly, Vol. 1, No. 1-45, 1994 September-1994 November (Box 3 (11-Publications), Folder 14)
  - The Hotline Weekly, Vol. 1, Vol. 2, No. 1-8, 1994 December-1995 February (Box 3 (11-Publications), Folder 15)
  - The Hotline Weekly, Vol. 2, No. 9-11, 1995 March-1995 April (Box 3 (11-Publications), Folder 16)
  - The Hotline Weekly, Vol. 2, No. 24-33, 1995 June-1995 August (Box 3 (11-Publications), Folder 17)
  - The Hotline Weekly, Vol. 2, No. 34-42, 1995 September-1995 October (Box 3 (11-Publications), Folder 18)
  - The Hotline Weekly, Vol. 2, No. 43-Vol. 3 No. 4, 1995 November-1996 January (Box 3 (11-Publications), Folder 19)
  - The Hotline Weekly, Vol. 3, No. 5-12, 1996 February-1996 March (Box 3 (11-Publications), Folder 20)
  - The Hotline Weekly, Vol. 3, No. 13-25, 1996 April-1996 June (Box 3 (11-Publications), Folder 21)
  - The Hotline Weekly, Vol. 3, No. 26-34, 1996 July-1996 August (Box 3 (11-Publications), Folder 22)
  - The Hotline Weekly, Vol. 3, No. 35-47, 1996 September-1996 November (Box 4 (11-Publications), Folder 1)
  - The Hotline Weekly, Vol. 3, No. 48- Vol. 4, No. 4, December 1996-January 1997 (Box 4 (11-Publications), Folder 2)
  - The Hotline Weekly, Vol. 4, No. 5-10, February-March 1997 (Box 4 (11-Publications), Folder 3)
  - Ramparts, 1967 June-1967 September (Box 4 (11-Publications), Folder 4)
  - Ramparts, 1968 January-1968 August (Box 4 (11-Publications), Folder 5)
  - Ramparts, 1968 September-1968 October (Box 4 (11-Publications), Folder 6-7)
- Melich Publications, Speeches, and Editing Work, 1957-2007; 12; 1.4 cubic ft.
  This series contains articles written by Tanya Melich as well as her master's thesis, "Youth Politics: A Study of Cliques Within the Association of New York State Young Republican Clubs, 1932-1959." There are copies of speeches she gave on various occasions. There is also information relating to Melich's editing work on an autobiography for Thomas E. Dewey. The materials relating to Dewey include two chapters of his autobiography, the transcript of a lengthy interview he conducted with reporter Harlan B. Phillips in 1957, some background research on Dewey conducted by Phillips, and chronologies.
  Also included in this series are files related to a book Melich worked on for Dan Yankelovich in 1984. Melich interviewed David Cohen, Betty Friedan, George Lodge, Samuel D. Proctor, Leon Shapiro, and others for their comments on certain chapters of the manuscript. The David Cohen material includes several IBM magcards which were recorded text as it was typed onto paper with a typewriter. The cards could then be used to recall and reprint the text. There is a list of page numbers and their corresponding magcard numbers. The Yankelovich files also contain background research and early drafts of some chapters.
  - Articles, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (12-Melich Publications, Speeches, and Editing Work), Folder 1)
  - Materials for Thomas E. Dewey Biography—Background Through 1923, Undated (Box 1 (12-Melich Publications, Speeches, and Editing Work), Folder 2)
  - Materials for Thomas E. Dewey Biography—Chapter I, 1969 (Box 1 (12-Melich Publications, Speeches, and Editing Work), Folder 3)
  - Materials for Thomas E. Dewey Biography—Chapter II, 1969 (Box 1 (12-Melich Publications, Speeches, and Editing Work), Folder 4)
  - Materials for Thomas E. Dewey Biography—Correspondence and Memorandums, 1957 (Box 1 (12-Melich Publications, Speeches, and Editing Work), Folder 5)